Thank you for watching!
I'm going to get my lunch.
Wow, it's so luxurious.
I'm going to eat it with my mouth open.
I'm going to eat it.
Here we go!
Ta-da!
Awesome!
I've got my hair and makeup done.
Today is the 4th day of the tour.
We're going to Nagoya Park.
Unfortunately, Hitoka is off today.
The five of us,
and the Sanrio characters,
and everyone who's a friend of mine,
and Fabrin,
we're going to work together to do our
best at Nagoya Park.
I'm looking forward to it.
And I'm going to work hard with Fabrin
to do my best at Nagoya Park.
How is it?
This time, Hitoka came up with the
members' hair styles.
I'm wearing a normal school uniform.
I'm feeling good.
I've only had vegetable juice for
breakfast today.
I'm hungry.
Ta-da!
Wow!
I got a bento box that looks like this.
I'm hungry, so I'm going to eat.
The dress I'm wearing today is a gift
from Canamin.
Thank you for watching.
I'm going to use TikTok to get it fast.
I got the nail polish.
What about Aki-chan's nail polish?
Is it okay?
What is it called? Kisuminbaori?
Go...Goninbaori?
Goninbaori?
I'm wearing a gold necklace right now.
Please take care of me.
It's Goninbaori.
Why is it Goninbaori?
Why?
I think I've never heard of it.
That's it.
I think it would be nice if Hiyori-chan
talks.
I'll do it.
Hiyori is...
You have to do the facial expression.
Hiyori can't talk, but I can.
Don't talk.
That's it. Bye bye.
Tenten camera.
Good morning.
Today is Nagoya Park.
It was a mess.
Hito-chan came up with my hair style.
I'm wearing a half-twin bun.
How is it?
How much is it?
Is it too high?
I had a lunch box with tofu and it was
so good.
I can eat as many tofu as I want.
I heard that I got wings. Let's see.
This mask is my favorite one.
This is a popular one.
The color of the string is different.
Look at this. It's made in pink.
I can't focus.
I did it!
I don't think I've ever taken a picture
of my hand this close.
I'll do my best.
Bye bye.
Nagoya people, please wait a little
longer.
Oh, it's over.
Nagoya people, thank you very much.
I'll do my best.
Bye bye.
Look at this.
Hitochan goods.
It's not goods.
I can't stop Hitochan power.
I came to see this today.
I thought I'd show you Hitochan.
It's cute.
It's good.
It's like this.
Look, it's Hitochan.
It's Hitochan.
It's cute.
The red of Hitochan.
I got it.
Red.
I can't see.
What kind of friend are you?
I'm a friend of Hito.
I see.
What about you, Aki?
I'm a friend of Hito.
Babysitter full of laughter
Red, it's true.
What do you buy and exchange?
Nagayashi-chan.
That's right.
Sugokiya's miso-nikomi udon is
delicious.
I've never eaten Sugokiya.
I like it.
I always go to Yamamoto-ya.
Su-chan.
Odan-bun.
And Su-chan.
Your face is similar.
Su-chan's face.
I'm an image model.
I'm a model of PIORIN.
Cute.
Bye bye!
Let's go home with the wings.
How?
Thank you for watching.
I'm going to eat it.
It says, one for each.
One for each member.
I'm going to eat it.
I want to eat it.
I can guess what you're going to do.
I don't know.
I don't know what you're going to do.
I think we did it.
I think it's pretty good.
I have to watch the video.
I don't know much about it.
That's amazing.
I'm doing it for the animals.
I think I'm more excited than usual.
I'm a little anxious and nervous.
I think this will be a different kind
of live performance than usual.
I'm nervous.
I'll do my best.
Let's calm down.
I'm done with my make-up.
Good morning.
I'm in Nagoya Park.
We are together today.
Yes, it's my first time to come here.
Nice to meet you.
I'm alone.
I'm wearing a mask today.
I'm wearing a mask and a red one.
I got a power from Hitoka.
I'll sing a good song.
You are strong.
I'm strong.
I'll do my best.
I'm nervous because I have to sing a
part of Hitoka's part.
I'm nervous because I have a different
feeling from usual.
I'll do my best while enjoying.
Let's enjoy together.
Did you change the way you sing?
Do you sing in the 0 bar?
Don't look at me, I'm sure it's sunny.
Are you laughing?
The song is spreading out, so I'll try
not to go to the front row.
I'll make a line behind the stage.
I want you to look at it.
I want to make sure everyone is
correct.
I'll go to the 6th row.
The position of the sidearm has
changed.
As I did in the rehearsal.
July sidearm.
You are here.
It's here.
It's my first time.
I want you to do it right now.
Hold it so that it doesn't escape.
And go down.
Please say hello to me.
1,2,3,4,5,6.
We are CHO.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Please support us.
I'm in love! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Wow! Wow! Wow! Wow!
I'm in love! I'm in love!
The first day of the concert
Thank you for coming.
Thank you for your cooperation.
What?
Donut?
Is this a donut?
It looks delicious.
It's big.
It's bigger than my face.
It's about 10 minutes before the show.
Look at my hair today.
I got a perm.
This tour is a three-time lock-on.
So I have to fix my hair before that.
So I got a perm today.
A very rarely hair perm.
I'm not rare.
I ate curry bread.
It's like a snack.
I had lunch and lunch box.
And I ate curry bread.
I'll charge my curry bread.
I'll do my best for the performance.
I'll do my best.
What?
I don't know if I can do nail art well.
I put on glitter.
I put on nail polish.
Bye bye.
I'll do my best.
1,2,3,Go!
Thank you for watching!
I'm going to do my best.
I'll do my best.
Thank you.
It's dangerous.
Everyone, please do your best.
I'll start with Kanae's part.
Yes.
I'll start.
Please.
Thank you for coming to the heart-
throbbing tour 2022 of the midsummer,
which witnessed a particular heart-
throbbing feeling with our Produce 101.
I'm Kanami Fujino, aka Kanami, the
super heart-throbbing blue.
Before I start my performance, I'd like
to ask the audience to be careful of the
line.
I'll be performing soon.
Today's performance will be on the day
of the super heart-throbbing red,
but we'll do our best to enjoy it, so I
hope you'll enjoy it with us.
I'm Kanami Fujino, aka Kanami, the
super heart-throbbing blue.
Let's have fun together!
Thank you!
Please wait for us!
Hitoka! Haruka!
Hiyori! Chako! Let's rock on!
It was pretty strong.
Please.
Good luck.
Good luck for Hitoka.
Thank you for your support.
I'll be back next time.
See you.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
Good job, everyone.
Everyone is clapping.
I'm relieved.
Thank you for your hard work.
It was the first time.
It was fun.
It's been a while since we were in
Nagoya.
It was amazing.
Everyone was smiling so much.
You can tell by the masks.
We have more people now.
It's amazing.
Thank you for the hub.
We did our best for the first day!
Next time, we'll do our best to go to
Nagoya and Osaka with 6 people.
Please wait for us!
Thank you!
I was happy to be with you. Thank you!
We've completed the Nabe Park.
I feel relieved.
We've done a lot of things before the
concert.
We've covered the song.
Really?
Ta-da!
We've been given the words from Hitoka.
We've introduced ourselves today.
She agreed with us.
She said she'll be with us forever.
I'm glad.
I'm glad that she said so.
I was thinking about you and singing
your part.
It was perfect.
Yeah.
That's right.
Cute.
Next is
Hokkaido.
My favorite Hokkaido.
Yay!
Let's do our best to hold it someday.
We will do our best.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
It was Nagoya Kouen.
About a year ago?
It was in August.
I heard that you were there.
I was there.
I'm glad that
we could hold it.
I want to go there again.
Anyway,
I'm glad that we could hold it.
We were relieved.
We did our best.
We were planning to release
the video.
I'm glad that
many people wanted to see us.
I'm glad that many people wanted to see
us.
It was warm.
Applause and smiles
were warm.
I like everyone's smiles.
I'm glad.
We haven't done a live show
with five people
since we became a super fan.
It was the first time.
We had a live show
with five people.
I felt that
the fans' kindness and warmth
were supported by everyone.
We don't cry
at our usual live shows.
When we stand on the stage,
we remember various things.
We were like
ah...
in front of everyone.
We were like
forgiving each other.
We were forgiving each other.
It makes us happy
when we think about it later.
We can make a face like this
when we are with the fans.
We can say these words together.
I think this is
a good relationship with the fans.
Being in a team is nice.
I think so.
We had
some parts this time.
The part
when all the members
took a part.
It's rare to hear that kind of voice.
I remember the song I don't usually
play.
I think 6 of us are the strongest.
I hope you come to see us again.
We will come back with 6 members.
I think your support has reached the
people.
Please come to see us again.
Thank you for your continued support.
See you again.
Let's dance together.
Please come to see us again. Osaka
people!
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
See you next time.
Wow.
Iceק Rabbit!
Amazing.
How cool.
To give such applause to our fans,
We want to step up our performance as a
group.
We want to perform as well as the other
groups.
I'm looking forward to seeing the
smiles on their faces.
I want to make a lot of memories.
I think it'll be fun if we can go to
different places.
October 22nd is...
Let's go!
To the special performance!
We'll be waiting!
The city of light is sparkling
As if my heart is a sunny pattern
I play the sound of a puddle
And play the rainbow piano
I wonder why
When I smile, it's like the world is
shining
I can turn my umbrella and feel relaxed
I can't walk without it
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere
I wonder if it's cold and wet somewhere
I want to share my feelings with you
The scenery I've never seen before
Let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye
Thank you for yesterday
The city after the rain is colored
On the canvas of my damaged heart
I draw fragments of the future
It will guide me
I can say it now, the reason for my
tears
When I'm lost, I remember right away
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of the rain drops
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a flower, the sound of
the rain drops
I wear a rainbow dress